This is it. It's four rooms and a bath.
就是这里. 有四个房间和一个卫生间.
This entrance hall is small, but look,
这个门厅很小, 不过 你看,
it leads to a nice big living room.
走进去是个不错的大的客厅.
This side faces south. It gets a lot of light.
这一面朝南. 有充足的阳光.
This is the dining room.
这是餐厅.
The woodwork's just lovely, isn't it?
木头家具很漂亮, 不是吗?
You'll notice that all the floors are hardwood.
你们会注意到所有的地板都是硬木的.
The kitchen is through here.
通过这里就是厨房.
Lots of cupboards.
有很多碗橱.
Dishwasher and disposal.
洗碗机和垃圾处理机.
There's a washer dryer in the basement.
那里有洗衣干衣两用机 在地下室.
You're allowed to use it.
你们可以使用那个.
And this is the bedroom.
还有这个是卧室.
Lots of closet space!
很多衣橱空间!
The bathroom's right next door.
卫生间就在隔壁.
It's fully updated with new fixtures.
里面全部配上了最新设施.
And more closet space.
和更大的橱柜空间.
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样?
I'm not doing all the laundry.
我才不会洗全部的衣服.